A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.37 (A2012) FA472
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.37 (A2012)
1989-2009
bulk
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation
FA472
64.87 Cubic Feet 49 record storage boxes, 1 letter document box, and 1 oversize box
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Project files transferred to the RAC by Rockefeller Foundation, 2012.
Arrangement
Records are primarily arranged by Program, with some materials arranged by the RF traditional series numbers.
Records are arranged as received. Within folders, materials are primarily arranged in reverse chronological order.
Conditions Governing Access
Records more than 10 years old are open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist. RAC is unable to provide access to obsolete media and original digital media. In addition separated media may not yet have undergone stabilization procedures. When feasible, a digital surrogate may be created via special order. All applicable charges will apply.
Separated Materials
Special Formats (audio, film, video, digital media, library materials, memorabilia, oversize, and photographic material) have been separated from the body of the collection. All pertinent items are assigned a unique separation number, as noted. Requests to access open special formats should reference the unique separation number.
Scope and Contents
Grant administration files and related materials.
- AC.2012.036: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.37, 1989-2005; AC_2012_036; 5.26 Cubic Feet 4 standard record storage boxes, R3943-R3946.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), 1989-2005; AC_2012_036_1; 5.26 Cubic Feet 4 record storage boxes
    - RF 99001 #706 - TAMIL NADU AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (INDIA) - GENETIC ENGINEERING OF RICE FOR THE MANAGEMENT OF FUNGAL DISEASES, 1998-2004 (Box R3943)
    - RF 99001 #724 - INTERNATIONAL RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE (PHILIPPINES) - TRANSGENIC INDICA RICES SUITABLE FOR EASTERN INDIA, 1998-2004 (Box R3943)
    - RF 99001 #734 - ZHEJIANG AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (CHINA) - BIOTECHNOLOGY CAREER FELLOWSHIP FOR SHU QINGYAO, 1999-2004 (Box R3943)
    - RF 99001 #737 - FUDAN UNIVERSITY (CHINA) - BIOTECHNOLOGY CAREER FELLOWSHIP FOR TANG KEXUAN, 1999-2004 (Box R3943)
    - RF 99001 #747 - CENTRAL RESEARCH INSTITUTE FOR FOOD CROPS (INDONESIA) - RICE CULTIVARS IN INDONESIA, 1997-2003 (Box R3943)
    - RF 99001 #755 - UNIVERSITY OF BARODA - PYRICULARIA ORYZAE, 1989-2005 (Box R3943)
    - RF 98006 #41; RF 99004 #42 - RF 99004 #42 - KENYA AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH INSTITUTE - MAIZE STREAK VIRUS (MSV) RESISTANCE IN AFRICA, 1996-2005 (Box R3944)
    - RF 99001 #782 - PEKING UNIVERSITY - ANTI-RICE LEAF BLIGHT, 1990-2002 (Box R3944)
    - RF 99002 - INITIATIVES FOR DEVELOPMENT AND EQUITY IN AFRICAN AGRICULTURE, 1996-2003 (Box R3944)
    - RF 99002 - INITIATIVES FOR DEVELOPMENT AND EQUITY IN AFRICAN AGRICULTURE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1996-2003 (Box R3944)
    - RF 99006 #145 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - PROMISING POTATO GENOTYPES IN EASTERN UGANDA, 1997-2001 (Box R3945)
    - RF 99006 #180 - KENYATTA UNIVERSITY (KENYA) - SOIL PRODUCTIVITY AND LOW-INPUT TECHNOLOGIES ON SMALLHOLDER FARMS, 1999-2001 (Box R3945)
    - RF 99006 #181 - UNIVERSITY OF NAIROBI - EFFECTS OF MAIZE/SESAME ROTATION CROPPING AND STRIGA, 1998-2004 (Box R3945)
    - RF 99007 #46 - CENTER FOR RESEARCH AND ADVANCED STUDIES OF THE NATIONAL POLYTECHNIC INSTITUTE (CINVESTAV)(MEXICO) - ALUMINUM TOLERANCE AND CEREALS, 1996-2004 (Box R3945)
    - RF 99009 #209 - FAMILY PLANNING ASSOCIATION OF NEW ZEALAND - COMMUNICATE ICPD PLAN OF ACTION TO PUBLIC AND POLICYMAKERS, 1995-2004 (Box R3945)
    - RF 99009 #210 - AUSTRALIAN REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH ALLIANCE - POST-CAIRO EDUCATION PROGRAM, 1994-2004 (Box R3945, Box R3946)
    - RF 99009 #214 - POPULATION COUNCIL - TRANSITION TO ADULTHOOD IN BANGLADESH, EGYPT, PAKISTAN, S. AFRICA AND VIETNAM, 1999-2004 (Box R3946)
    - RF 99009 #214 - POPULATION COUNCIL - TRANSITION TO ADULTHOOD IN BANGLADESH, EGYPT, PAKISTAN, S. AFRICA AND VIETNAM - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1999-2004 (Box R3946)
- AC.2012.051: Rockefeller Foundation records, grants, 1989-2007; AC_2012_051; 7.89 Cubic Feet 6 standard record storage boxes
  Arrangement
  Arranged by program.
  Records are arranged as received. Within folders, materials are primarily arranged in reverse chronological order.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), 7.89 Cubic Feet 6 record storage boxes
    - RF 99009 #215 Center for Cultural and Technical Interchange Between East and West - Improving Policy Dialogue in Asia-Pacific Region, 1999-2004 (Box R3947)
    - RF 99009 #220 University of Cape Coast (Ghana)- Ideational Change and Reproductive Behavior, 1993-2005 (Box R3947)
    - RF 99011 Contadores de Estorias Producoes LTDA. - Latin American Performance Network (3+ 1 Suppl), 1991-2003 (Box R3947)
    - RF 99013 American Council of Learned Societies - Fellowship Program for Humanities Scholars, 1999-2002 (Box R3948)
    - (Strategic Alliance: Rockefeller Foundation - California Endowment) (4= 1 Suppl.), 1997-2003 (Box R3948)
    - RF 99017 #12 Strategic Concepts in Organizing and Policy Education - California Works for Better Health Project, 2000-2005 (Box R3948)
    - RF 99017 #13 East L.A. Community Corporation - California Works for Better Health Project, 2000-2004 (Box R3948)
    - RF 99017 #21 Catholic Charities of the Diocese of Fresno - California Works for Better Health Project, 2000-2006 (Box R3949)
    - RF 99020 (Soils Management to Overcome Yield Constrainst) (2 folders), 1989-2003 (Box R3949)
    - RF 99020 #207 Kenyatta University (Kenya) - Studentships and Related Expensesfor Research on Soil Productivity and Low-Input Technologies on SmallHolder Farms, 1999-2003 (Box R3949)
    - RF 99020 #218 Ongecha, John - Soil Fertility and Bean Infestation in Maize-Bean Systems, 1999-2003 (Box R3949)
    - RF 99021 #104 Population Council - Microbicidal Compounds to Prevent Transmission of HIV (3 folders), 1993-2005 (Box R3949)
    - RF 99021 #105 Diamonds Aids Research Center - Microbicide Network, 1998-2003 (Box R3950)
    - RF 99021 #107 Rockefeller University - Microbicide Network, 1998-2003 (Box R3950)
    - RF 99021 #108 University of California - Microbicide Network (Davis), 1998-2004 (Box R3950)
    - RF 99021 #109 University of Virginia - Epididymal-Specific Transcription Factors and Secreted Proteins and MaleContraceptives (2+1 Suppl.), 1996-2004 (Box R3950)
    - RF 99021 #110 Vanderbilt University - Schering Network, 1998-2003 (Box R3950)
    - RF 99021 #111 Westphalian Wilhelms University (Germany) - Sperm Metabolism and Male Contraception, 1996-2004 (Box R3950)
    - RF 99021 #112 University of Turku (Finland)- Immortalization of Epididymal Cells, 1996-2003 (Box R3950)
    - RF 98027 #381; RF 99024 #382 Bang on a Can - Original Music Work, "Joy", 1999-2003 (Box R3951)
    - RF 99021 #116 PrinceHenry's Institute of Medical Research (Australia)- Implantation Network/WHO, 1998-2004 (Box R3951)
    - RF 99021 #117 Oregon Health Services University - Implantation Network/WHO, 1998-2004 (Box R3951)
    - RF 99021 #119 Chinese Academy of Sciences - Instituteof Zoology - Research on Male Contraception and Implantation, 1993-2004 (Box R3951)
    - RF 99026 #125 Ingrid Washinawatok El-Issa Flying Eagle Woman Fund for Peace - Work with Indigenous People of the World, 2000-2007 (Box R3951)
    - RF 99026 #92 Harvard University - Gay-Lesbian-Bisexual-Transgender Societal Equality in the 21st Century, 1999-2004 (Box R3951)
    - RF 99027 #5 Hispanics in Philanthropy - Education and Networking Program, 2000-2004 (Box R3951)
    - RF 99037 #11 Training and Research Support Centre (Zimbabwe) - Equity Gauge Initiative, 2000-2003 (Box R3951)
    - RF 99037 #5 International Centre for Diarrhoeal Disease Research, Bangladesh - Effects of Poverty Alleviation Programs on Health, 2000-2004 (Box R3951)
    - RF 99038 #4 World Health Organization (Switzerland) - Intercluster Vaccine Research Initiative, 1999-2004 (Box R3951)
    - RF 99040 #99 Sakhi for South Asian Women - Reproductive Health Research in India (1+1 Suppl.), 2000-2004 (Box R3951)
    - RF 99040 #100 Universityof Ibadan (Nigeria) - Reproductive Health Education and Services for Adolescnets in Nigeria, 2000-2004 (Box R3952)
    - RF 99040 #101 Family Planning Association of Kenya - Reproductive Health Services for Young People, 1993-2003 (Box R3952)
    - RF 99042 #83 Smithsonian Institution - Meetings Between U.S. and Iranian Museum Officials, 2000-2004 (Box R3952)
    - RF 99045 #74 Philadelphia Folklore Project - Youth Folk Art Ensembles, 2000-2004 (Box R3952)
    - RF 99045 #76 University of Maine - Revive Language and Culture on Native American Communities of Maine, 2000-2004 (Box R3952)
    - RF 99052 #2 Curatio International Foundation (Georgia) - Health Research for Responsive Healthcare System, 2000-2004 (Box R3952)
    - RF 99052 #4 Nepal Health Research Council - Health Research Award (1+ 1 Suppl.), 2000-2004 (Box R3952)
- AC.2012.065: Rockefeller Foundation records, grants management office, 1994-2009; AC 2012:065; 9.2 Cubic Feet 7 standard record storage boxes
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), 3.94 Cubic Feet 3 record storage boxes
    - Medical Research Council (South Africa) - Health Research Award, RF 99052 #5, 2000-2004 (Box R3953)
    - National institute of Public Health (Mexico) Health Research Award, RF 99052 #6, 2000-2001 (Box R3953)
    - Brazilian Institute for Consumer Protection - Health Research Award, RF 99052 #8, 2000-2004 (Box R3953)
    - National Institute for Medical Research (Tanzania) - Health Research Award, RF 99052 #10, 2000-2004 (Box R3953)
    - Female Participation in African Education (4 + 2 Suppl.), RF 99055, 1996-2004 (Box R3954, Box R3953)
    - Forum for African Women Educationalists, Ghana Chapter - Capacity Building and Technical Support, RF 99055 #179, 2000-2004 (Box R3955)
    - Maendeleo Ya Wanawake Organization (Kenya) - Healthy Futures Project, RF 99055 #188, 1999-2003 (Box R3955)
    - South African Broadcasting Corproation - Takalani Sesame Outreach Project, RF 99055 #189, 1999-2002 (Box R3955)
    - National Humanities Center - Fellowship Program, RF 99057, 1999-2009 (Box R3955)
  - Assets and Capacities (AC), 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - Ahoka: Innovators for the Public - Strategies for Communicating System Changing, 2002 AC 102, 2002-2003 (Box R3955)
    - Umzingwane Aids Network (Zimbabwe) - Empowering Youth to Advocate Against Transmission of HIV, 2002 AC 106, 2000-2005 (Box R3955)
    - Zimbabwe Aids Prevention and Support Organization - Communication Processes to Fight Aids, 2002 AC 107, 2000-2005 (Box R3955)
    - Citizens Committee for New York City - New York City Fund (3 folders), 2002 AC 110, 1994-2004 (Box R3955)
    - (Assets Capacities - Communication for Social Change) - Multi-media Training Kits, 2002 AC 113, 2002-2003 (Box R3956)
    - Worldspace Foundation - General Support, 2002 AC 116, 2002-2003 (Box R3956)
    - African Network for Health Knowledge Management and Communication (Kenya) - Harnessing Communication and Information Technology for Community Health, 2002 AC 117, 2002-2003 (Box R3956)
    - (Assets and Capacities) - NATC Target Country Communication Assessment, 2002 AC 119, 2002-2004 (Box R3956)
      Separated Materials
      Special format items (audio, film, video, digital media, library materials, memorabilia, oversize, and photographic material) have been separated from the file. Each item is assigned a unique separation number, as noted. Requests to access open special formats should reference the unique separation number.
    - Panorama de las communicationes entre comunidades trasnacionales de America del Norte y Lantinoamerica - 2002 AC 119 - La Iniciativa de Comunicacion, 2012:065:001 (Box R3956)
    - Panorama de las communicationes entre communidades trasnacionales de America del norte y Latinoamerica - 2002 AC 112 - La Iniciativa de comunicacion, 2012:065:002 (Box R3956)
    - Directorio de medios en los Estados Unidos; Red de Interesados en Comunicciones Transnacionales (Resultado de la Investigacion) 2002 AC 112, 2012:065:003 (Box R3956)
    - Decatur Memorial Foundation - Decatur Commmunity Partnership, 2002 AC 120, 2002-2005 (Box R3956)
    - Sound Portraits Productions - Storykiosk, 2002 AC 122, 2002-2004 (Box R3956)
    - Story Corps Vol.2 - 2002 AC 122 - Grantee: Sound Portraits Production, 2012:065:004 (Box R3956)
    - World Conservation Union (Switzerland) - Update Book, The Careless Technology, 2002 AC 201, 2002-2005 (Box R3956)
    - The Careless Technology - Ecology and International Development - 2002 ACC 201, 2012:065:005 (Box R3956)
    - Commune of Bellagio (Italy) - Computers for Local Public Schools, 2002 AC 217, 2002-2004 (Box R3956)
    - Harvard University - "HIV/AIDS and Business in Africa and Asia: Building Sustainable Partnerships," 2003 AC 201, 2002-2004 (Box R3956)
    - Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory - DNA Exhibit at NY Public Library, 2003 AC 202, 2002-2003 (Box R3956)
    - Rockefeller University - Event Celebrating 50th Anniversary of Discovery of DNA Structure, 2003 AC 203, 2003-2004 (Box R3956)
    - Virtue Foundation - Symposium to Commemorate Response to 9/11, 2003 AC 213, 2003-2004 (Box R3956)
    - Center for Strategic and International Studies - General Support, 2003 AC 215, 2003-2004 (Box R3956)
  - Africa Regional (AR), 3.94 Cubic Feet 3 record storage boxes
    - Getahun, Abebe - ACA: Non-Indigenous Fish in Ethiopia, 2001 AR 002, 2000-2004 (Box R3957)
    - Sogbedji, Jean Mianikpo - Sustaining Maize Yields in Togo, 2001 AR 003, 2000-2004 (Box R3957)
    - Arama, Peter F. - ACA: Russian Wheat Aphid Control in Kenya, 2001 AR 004, 1999-2001 (Box R3957)
    - Thoithi, Grace Njeri - ACA: Anthelmintic Activity of Medicinal Plants in Kenya, 2001 AR 006, 2000-2003 (Box R3957)
    - Kangire, Africano - ACA: Banana Cultivars in Uganda, 2001 AR 007, 1999-2004 (Box R3957)
    - Muluvi, Geoffrey Mwanza - ACA: Genetic Diversity of Moringa in Kenya, 2001 AR 010, 2000-2003 (Box R3957)
    - Contech, Abdul Rahman - ACA: Green Manure Cropping for Sustainable Soil Management in West Africa, 1999-2003 (Box R3957)
    - Opondo, Mary Magdalene - ACA: Gender and Tobacco Contract Farmers in Kenya, 1999-2003 (Box R3957)
    - Mburugu, Gitonga Nkanata - Nitrogen Fixation and Grain Yield in Soybeans, 2001 AR 015, 1999-2003 (Box R3957)
    - Wandahwa, Philip - ACA: Soybean Yields and Soil Fertility Management in Kenya, 2001 AR 022, 1999-2003 (Box R3957)
    - Isutsa, Dorcas K. - ACA: Passion Fruit in Kenya, 2001 AR 025, 1999-2004 (Box R3957)
    - Brown University - Meeting on Higher Education, 2001 AR 028, 2001-2003 (Box R3957)
    - Zimba, Godwin Mufwa Mannex - ACA: Zonocerus Elegans and Cassava in Malawi, 2001 AR 031, 1999-2004 (Box R3957)
    - Ekaya, Wellington N. - ACA: Land Use and Land Tenure Changes in Kajiado, Kenya, 2001 AR 032, 1999-2003 (Box R3957)
    - Mutisya, Dorothy Nduku - ACA: Role of Women in Soil Conservation in Kenya, 2001 AR 034, 1999-2003 (Box R3957)
    - Kinyua, Miriam Gaceri - ACA: Wheat Varieties and Lines for Marginal Areas in Kenya, 2001 AR 035, 1999-2003 (Box R3957)
    - Institute for Reproductive Health Training and Research (Kenya) - Private/Public Collaboration to Meet Needs of School Children, 2001 AR 039, 2001-2004 (Box R3957)
    - Forum for African Women Educationalists, Ghana Chapter - Sexual Maturation and Hygiene Practices, 2001 AR 043, 2001-2003 (Box R3957)
    - Forum for African Women Educationalists, Uganda Chapter - Kalangala Pilot Initiative, 2001-2004 (Box R3958)
    - Simiyu, Silas Masinde - ACA: Micro-Seismic Studies in Geothermal Exploration in Kenya, 2001 AR 055, 1999-2003 (Box R3958)
    - Mbarara University of Science and Technology (Uganda) - Control of Vectors of Tropical Parasitic Diseases in Man and Livestock, 2001 AR 059, 2001-2005 (Box R3958)
    - McMaster, John Maxwell - ACA: Domestic Violence Prevention Program, 2001 AR 060, 2000-2002 (Box R3958)
    - Cotton Products (U) Ltd. (Uganda) - Feminine Hygiene Protection Products in Uganda, 2001 AR 063, 2001-2004 (Box R3958)
    - African Studies Association - African and North American Higher Education Project, 2001 AR 068, 2001-2005 (Box R3958)
    - Kariuki, Samuel Mungai - ACA: Typhoid Diagnosis in Kenya, 2001 AR 070, 2000-2003 (Box R3958)
    - Sewram, Vikash - ACA: Medicinal Wild Plants and Esophageal Cancer, 2001 AR 071, 1999-2004 (Box R3958)
    - Wilson, David - ACA: AIDS Prevention Program in Zimbabwe's Schools, 2001 AR 072, 2000-2006 (Box R3958)
    - Rukunga, Geoffrey M. - ACA: Traditional healers to Treat Malaria in Kenya, 2001 AR 073, 2001-2004 (Box R3958)
    - Mbagaya, Grace M. - ACA: Child Nutrition in Marachi, Kenya, 2001 AR 076, 2001-2004 (Box R3958)
    - Kenya Community Development Foundation - Indigenous philanthropic Initiatives, 201 AR 080, 2001-2003 (Box R3958)
    - Oluka, Silas Omoding - ACA: Physics Teaching in Uganda, 2001 AR 081, 1999-2004 (Box R3958)
    - Centre for African Family Studies (Kenya) - Monograph and Website on African Families, 2001 AR 084, 2001-2004 (Box R3958)
    - Abstracts on the Family Database for "Developing a Monograpn on East African Family Transformations" Project - 2001 AR 084, 2012:065:006
    - Teachers College, Columbia University - Research Approaches to Decentralization in East and Southern Africa, 2001 AR 087, 2001-2004 (Box R3959)
    - Federation on Women Lawyers - Kenya - Women's Rights Monitoring and Legal Awareness, 2001 AR 088, 2001-2004 (Box R3959)
    - Inter-University Council for East Africa (Uganda) - Training Program for University Administrators, 2001 AR 090, 2001-2004 (Box R3959)
    - Maseno University (Kenya) - Traditional Managmement of Sexual Maturation, 2002 AR 022, 2002-2004 (Box R3959)
    - Kyambobo University (Uganda) - Sexual Maturation, 2002 AR 026, 2002-2004 (Box R3959)
    - Egerton University (Kenya) - Sexual Maturation, 2002 AR 028, 2002-2004 (Box R3959)
    - Makerere University (Uganda) - MISR Sexual Maturation Project, 2002 AR 029, 2002-2004 (Box R3959)
    - Schooling Uganda Through Children's Eyes - Next Step - 2002 AR 029, 2012:065:007 (Box R3959)
    - International CropsResearch Institute for the Semi-Arid Tropics (India) - Conference on Rural Livelihoods and Poverty Reduction Policies, 2002 AR 034, 2002-2004 (Box R3959)
    - Mbarara University of Science and Technology (Uganda) - Internet Connectivity and Website, 2002 AR 039, 2002-2003 (Box R3959)
    - Association of African Universities (Ghana) - Conference on the Role of African Institutions in Building the African Union, 2002 AR 040, 2002-2004 (Box R3959)
    - Makerere University (Uganda) - Information for Development Stakeholders Meeting, 2002 AR 044, 2002-2003 (Box R3959)
- AC.2012.073: Rockefeller Foundation records, grants management office, 1992, 1996, 1998-2008; bulk; AC 2012:073; 17.55 Cubic Feet 13 standard record storage boxes, 1 letter document box, and 1 oversize box
  Records are primarily arranged by Program, with some materials arranged by the RF traditional series numbers.
  - Bellagio Study and Conference Center, 120; 6.57 Cubic Feet 5 record storage boxes
    Conditions Governing Access
    Restricted - Fellowship Files - Open in 2027
    - Resident (Abaza, Mona), 2004-2005 (Box R3965)
    - Resident (Ackermann, Lourens W.H.), 2004-2005 (Box R3965)
    - Resident (Adams, Marilyn McCord), 2004-2005 (Box R3965)
    - Resident (Albats, Yevgenia Mark), 2004-2005 (Box R3965)
    - Resident (Alliston, April), 2004-2006 (Box R3965)
    - Resident (Anderson, Warwick Hugh M.)(C-Resident: Clarke, Adele E.), 2004-2005 (Box R3965)
    - Resident (Appleton, Jon Howard), 2004-2006 (Box R3965)
    - Resident (Armony, Ariel C.)(Co-resident: Crahan, Margaret E.), 2004-2005 (Box R3965)
    - Resident (Banerjee, Tridib), 2004-2006 (Box R3965)
    - Resident (Banfield, Ann M.), 2004-2006 (Box R3965)
    - Resident (Barnes, Peter Franklin), 2004-2005 (Box R3965)
    - Resident (Bayer, Ronald)(Co-Resident: Oppenheimer, Gerald), 2004-2005 (Box R3965)
    - Resident (Beard, Michael Crowell)(Co-Resident: Haydar, Adnan Fuad), 2004-2006 (Box R3965)
    - Resident (Berger, Karol), 2004-2005 (Box R3965)
    - Resident (Berger, Mark), 2004-2005 (Box R3965)
    - Resident (Binder, Amy J.), 2004-2005 (Box R3965)
    - Resident (Bizri, Hisham M.), 2004-2006 (Box R3965)
    - Resident (Blight, James George)(Co-Resident: Welch, David Andrew), 2004-2005 (Box R3965)
    - Resident (Boraine, Alexander Lionel), 2004-2005 (Box R3965)
    - Resident (Brooke, Stephen J.), 2004-2005 (Box R3965)
    - Resident (Brubeck, David Darius), 2004-2006 (Box R3965)
    - Resident (Busia, Abena Pokua A.), 2004-2005 (Box R3966)
    - Resident (Byrd, Rudolph P.), 2004-2005 (Box R3966)
    - Resident (Carney, Judith A.), 2004-2005 (Box R3966)
    - Resident (Castro, Yanira H.), 2004-2005 (Box R3966)
    - Resident (Caws, Mary Ann), 2004-2005 (Box R3966)
    - Resident (Cheng, Anita) (Co-Resident: Kiel, Ronaldo), 2004-2005 (Box R3966)
    - Resident (Chin, Marilyn Mei Ling), 2004-2005 (Box R3966)
    - Resident (Chin, Marilyn Mei Ling), 2004-2005 (Box R3966)
    - Resident (Chinalai, Lee J.)(Co-Resident: Chinalai, Vichai), 2004-2005 (Box R3966)
    - Resident (Cleveland, William Taylor), 2004-2005 (Box R3966)
    - Resident (Contreras, Frances Elizabeth)(Co-Resident: Gandara, Patricia C.), 2004-2005 (Box R3966)
    - Resident (Costanzo, William V.), 2004-2005 (Box R3966)
    - Resident (de Waal, Thomas Patrick), 2004-2006 (Box R3966)
    - Resident (Dehejia, Vidya), 2004-2009 (Box R3966)
      Restricted - Fellowship Files - Open in 2030
    - Resident (Del Rivero, Elena), 2004-2005 (Box R3966)
    - Resident (Dellora, Daryl G.)(Co-Resident: Hocking, John Frederick), 2003-2005 (Box R3966)
    - Resident (Diez, Francisco)(Co-Resident: McCoy, Jennifer Lynn), 2004-2005 (Box R3966)
    - Resident (Duggirala, Vasanta), 2004-2005 (Box R3966)
    - Resident (Engel, Barbara Apern), 2004-2005, 2011 (Box R3966)
      Restricted - Fellowship Files - Open in 2032
    - Resident (Farley, John), 2004-2005 (Box R3966)
    - Resident (Festinger, Richard), 2004-2005 (Box R3966)
    - Resident (Friedmann, Harriet), 2004-2005 (Box R3966)
    - Resident (Furberg, Curt Daniel), 2004-2005 (Box R3966)
    - Resident (Gaventa, John Price), 2004-2006 (Box R3966)
    - Resident (Gena, Peter), 2004-2005 (Box R3966)
    - Resident (Gibson, Katherine D.)(Co-Resident: Graham, Julie), 2004-2005 (Box R3966)
    - Resident (Gokhale, Manita Rajiv)(Co-Resident: Lal, Malashri), 2003-2005 (Box R3967)
    - Resident (Green, Sam), 2004-2005 (Box R3967)
    - Resident (Grindle, Merilee S.), 2004-2005 (Box R3967)
    - Resident (Guri-Rosenblit, Sarah), 2004-2005 (Box R3967)
    - Resident (Gute, Charles A.), 2004-2005 (Box R3967)
    - Resident (Hamilton, Lonnee Eileen), 2004-2005 (Box R3967)
    - Resident (Hartman, Karen Suzanne), 2004-2006 (Box R3967)
    - Resident (Hartmann, Michael E.)(Co-Resident: Klonowiecka-Milart, Agnieszka Marie), 2004-2006 (Box R3967)
    - Resident (Hasper, Graciela Viviana), 2005 (Box R3967)
    - Resident (Hersch, Fred S.), 2004-2005 (Box R3967)
    - Resident (Higginbotham, Elizabeth Starr), 2004-2005 (Box R3967)
    - Resident (Hollister, Robinson Gill), 2004-2005 (Box R3967)
    - Resident (Holloway, Karla F. C.), 2004-2005 (Box R3967)
    - Resident (Hongo, Garrett), 2001-2005 (Box R3967)
    - Resident (Howard, John), 2004-2005 (Box R3967)